你好，欢迎观看这个视频。
Hello, welcome to this video.
今天我们来学习如何使用实时字幕功能。
Today we will learn how to use the real-time subtitle feature.
首先，导入一个视频文件。
First, import a video file.
然后，点击标记开始按钮记录起始时间。
Then, click the mark start button to record the start time.
观看视频内容，结束时点击标记结束。
Watch the video content, and click mark end when finished.
添加字幕后，可以点击翻译按钮。
After adding subtitles, you can click the translate button.
系统会优先使用记忆库和语料库。
The system will prioritize using the memory and corpus.
如果没有匹配，会自动调用翻译API。
If there is no match, it will automatically call the translation API.
翻译完成后，可以自定义字幕样式。
After translation, you can customize the subtitle style.
调整字幕位置、大小、颜色等参数。
Adjust subtitle position, size, color and other parameters.
最后，导出为SRT文件保存。
Finally, export as an SRT file to save.
感谢观看，祝你使用愉快！
Thanks for watching, hope you enjoy using it!